I want to assure you that wherever you are, Jesus is there.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Jesus is going to give us His Word - prayer language
And whatever word we pronounce now is not just a word - that is the language for you.
Believe it.
I'm not going to raise a prayer point, but I'm going to say it according to God's will,
according to Heaven. So please, be ready.
Don't think, "You want me to say after you" - No, that is not it.
This is a word for you to destroy whatever temple that is disturbing you.
So please, are you ready?
There's one thing you need to do.
Have you forgiven those who sinned against you?
Whether you are right or wrong, you have to forgive.
Allow your heart to talk about this.
So you can just conclude here. When you leave from here, you will follow it up.
If there's anyone somewhere that has wronged you - so painful -
and you have said you would never forgive.
In your heart here, take that decision that "Yes, it is over!"
So when you leave from here, you can follow up the restitution.
Right now, forgive us as we forgive those who sin against us.
The Bible say, when you stand to pray, forgive.
Tell your neighbour.
When you stand to pray, forgive.
I can't hear you.
Again
When you stand to pray, forgive.
You just stand and you want to pray. You just have to forgive.
Whether you are right or wrong, put it behind you.
Because you need a free spirit. You don't need to imprison your spirit.
When you imprison your spirit, it cannot attract God's Spirit.
To hold offence, whether you are right or wrong, you are imprisoning your spirit.
Now, it is time to attract God's Spirit.
I release every spirit that holds offence.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Sometimes you need intervention, you need someone to come in.
You don´t know that you need someone to help you.
I release every spirit that holds offence.
Every spirit that holds offence - be released in the name of Jesus!
Yes, we are saved with authority.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Sometimes you may not even know.
The dividends of forgiveness is freedom.
When you forgive, you receive freedom.
That is just it. I want you to know that.
The dividends of forgiveness is what?
Freedom.
How can you continue caging yourself?
Whether you are accused or you are accuser,
for how long will you continue to cage yourself?
This world is a journey - a marathon.
You cannot continue caging yourself.
The Bible says, I will set a table before you in the presence of your what?
Enemies!
Eh hen, what else again?
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers, wherever you are, we are saying to you -
the cage of sickness, poverty, isolation is as a result of forgiveness.
Whether you are the accused or the accuser,
you find yourself in a cage of poverty,
you find yourself in a cage of affliction,
it must be - that is the root.
The root of poverty is unforgiveness.
The root of affliction is unforgiveness.
The root of isolation, depression is unforgiveness.
Unforgiveness is the root. Tell your neighbour.
The root of isolation is unforgiveness.
The root of affliction is unforgiveness.
The root of depression is unforgiveness.
The root of poverty is unforgiveness.
Whether you are the accused or the accuser, that is the root.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, right now, it is time to begin to release yourself.
You have been in that cage of poverty, isolation, affliction, setback;
please, forgive whether you are the accused or the accuser.
Jesus said, "Forgive them, they don´t know what they are doing".
You are included!
Begin to forgive. I release your spirit, in the name of Jesus!
I release your spirit, in the name of Jesus!
To release your spirit is for you to realise, "Ah, no! What is the gain?"
Ask yourself, "Ok, this man has wronged me. This woman has wronged me"
and you now hold that offence.
For how many years now are you holding that offenve? What is your gain?
Leave it for God. Don't worry yourself. Tell your neighbour.
Leave it for God. Don't worry yourself.
Our life is under repair.
Something that is under repair which is yearning to be repaired, not destroyed.
Say, "Mercy!"
Mercy!
I can´t hear you!
Viewers all over the world!
Mercy!
Again and again.
This is what you need now.
Open your lips now and say, "Have mercy on me, Son of David!"
Have mercy on me, Son of David!
You yourself sit down and think about your life.
Every hope and every belief we had in the past -
when your children graduate and become a professor, you have everything you need.
If you become a manager of a company, you have everything you need.
Look at many homes today.
See homes, see families, see disunity.
There's disunity everywhere.
Mercy!
I can´t hear you!
That is it. Who needs mercy?
That is, holding unforgiveness. You are holding unforgiveness, and you need mercy.
It is not about your weakness - not about your setback.
Here I am.
Right now, open your lips and begin to bind your body, soul, spirit
to the will and purpose of God for your life.
Viewers all over the world, be bound, in the name of Jesus -
to the will and purpose of God, in the name of Jesus!
Your soul, spirit and body - be bound, in the name of Jesus!
Every spirit that stands to challenge you,
that stands to challenge everything about you -
every spirit that stands to challenge you, that stands to challenge your health -
begin to rebuke it, in the name of Jesus!
I loose that spirit!
Loose it, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You evil spirit!
You demon!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
I command that spirit that causes you sickness,
that causes you disease,
that causes you setback,
that causes you poverty.
I command that spirit right now!
You evil spirit, you demon, I curse you by name!
Demon in your business!
Demon in your health!
Demon in your finances!
Demon in your marriage!
Demon in your health!
Demon in your business!
Demon!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Demons are already manifesting in the lives of the people.
The fire of the Holy Ghost is revealing them wherever they are right now.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen. Spirits that kill, steal and destroy are being exposed
in different parts of the church right now.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Watch and see how people are vomiting out poisonous substances from their system.
In the might name of Jesus Christ!
The name Jesus - above all!
All knees shall bow; all tongues shall confess.
Engage your spirit.
We are not sowing to this flesh but to the Spirit
Begin to engage your spirit right now!
The name Jesus!
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Open your lips right now.
Begin to loose that infirmity.
I loose that infirmity, sickness, disease!
Be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
That disease in your blood, kidneys, liver, bones - be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to loose it! Open your lips!
Loose it!
That fibroid - loose it!
Be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
Talk to that spirit, infirmity!
Begin to talk to that sickness!
Loose it, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips! Begin to talk!
Talk!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
You sickness, you disease, I command you - leave my people!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
I command them out!
Out, in your blood!
Out, in your kidneys!
Command them out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Be flushed out!
Command that disease, sickness! Open your lips! Mean it with all your heart!
Wherever that disease is located, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
It could be in your blood, kidneys, liver - out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command that weakness, if there is any weakness that is standing against you -
remember, it is not about your weakness, it is not about your setback;
I say, submit, in the name of Jesus!
Surrender, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever you might have taken, eaten in your dream or from the table of your enemy -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever you might have taken in the dream from the table of your enemy -
I flush them out, in the name of Jesus, by the power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
By the power of the Holy Ghost, Holy Ghost!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a disease or infirmity Jesus cannot cure.
Never a burden Jesus cannot bear.
Receive freedom!
Receive a relief!
Freedom!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to talk in your freedom!
Freedom!
Breakthrough, in your health!
Freedom, in your business!
Breakthrough, in your finances!
Freedom, in your marriage!
Breakthrough, in your family!
Freedom!
Breakthrough, in your career!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I'm waiting to hear the voice of breakthrough from you!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I believe!
The voice I'm hearing is the voice of freedom.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I hear the voice of freedom!
If that voice is from you, right now, begin to act freedom!
How do you act freedom?
Share your testimony with your colleague!
That is how to act freedom.
"I was having a headache but right now, it is gone!"
Amen!
When I say 'act freedom', I hear the noise.
People begin to talk to themselves.
If you are giving testimony, will you give it to yourself?
No!
So you just...
Brother, come.
When I came here today in the morning - I'm sharing my testimony -
I was having some little pain here. But it is gone now!
And the business, the debt - it is paid! My spirit is telling me, it is paid!
So face your neighbour and tell your neighbour your testimony.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In Jesus' name!
Viewers, begin to act freedom, act breakthrough, share your testimony with your neighbour.
Tell them your testimony!
That is it.
It is not a drama - it is real; it is reality.
I'm telling you what is happening over there!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
Yes, that matter has been settled.
So, write it down. You begin to act freedom from now.
You have received God's mercy.
And you know, when you talk of mercy - undeserved person receives mercy.
Son of David, have mercy on me.
Thank you. Hallelujah.
I confirm this declaration - declaration of freedom,
declaration of breakthrough, be confirmed, in the name of Jesus!
Declaration of freedom, breakthrough - be confirmed, in the name of Jesus!
Let your heart agree with me. This is what is going on in your life.
Right now, don't reject it.
It is declared that you are free!
Enough is enough; you are released!
You are released, in the name of Jesus!
I can't hear you.
Amen!
Open your lips.
Commit your career, business, finances, business partner - God's intervention!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I want you to know that God is on top of your case.
Take my word and write it down. These are prophetic words.
When God is on top of your case, your case is settled.
So, begin to rejoice!
Right now, your nation.
Whatever you have as a contact for your nation, prayer for your nation.
God's intervention in your economy, among your leaders.
God's intervention.
Right now, commit your nation into God's hand.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Ask God to listen to the voice of your leaders.
Come into the matter.
God's intervention.
We ask for mercy.
God's intervention in your nation's economy, your leaders.
God's intervention.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name. Amen.
Right now, if there is anyone in our midst who is still doubting, I strengthen your faith!
Let your faith be strengthened!
Receive faith to believe!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Right now, cover yourself with the blood of Jesus!
Viewers, begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus!
You are designed for freedom; you are designed for breakthrough.
Right now, cover yourself with the blood of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Amen.
Many of us that are here to rededicate ourselves and those who are just knowing the Lord,
say after me,
Lord Jesus, come into my heart;
wash me with Your precious blood.
Make my heart Your channel; a channel of shining light.
Make my heart a channel of humility.
Make my heart a channel of love where there is hatred.
Make my heart a channel of forgiveness where there is injury.
Make my heart a channel of pardon.
Make my heart a channel of shining light where there is darkness.
Make my heart a channel of obedience where there is disobedience.
Thank You, Lord, for dying in my place.
I believe.
Thank You, Lord, for Your Salvation. In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear your Amen.
Amen
You received Christ?
Yes!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Now, your voice should be the voice of testimony, not the voice of complaint.
"Do you know, I still have pain here."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour, "My voice is the voice of testimony".
My voice is the voice of testimony.
That is it.